Guide to the Rick Lazio Papers, 1981–2005
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES I. PRE-CONGRESSIONAL PAPERS
  - Campaign Files
    - Campaign and Voting Research Material, (Campaign Guide For Congressional Candidates, Voting Rights Report), Apr-Oct 1992 (Box 22)
    - Civic Organizations Mailing Lists, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Conservatives (reference), Jul 1992 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence, Constituents and Congressional Colleagues Seeking Legislative Support, Nov 1992-Feb 1993 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence, (Thank You Letters), May 1992 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence, (Letters of Congratulations), Nov-Dec 1992; (3 folders) (Box 22)
    - Debate Preparation Notes, (Debate With Tom Downey – Handwritten Notes, Background Material), Aug-Oct 1992; (2 folders) (Boxes 22, 157)
    - Downey, Tom, (Press Clippings), May 1989-Dec 1992 (Box 22)
    - Election Results, Presidential Percentages, Congressional Results, 1986-1992 (Box 22)
    - Endorsement Press Release and Press Clippings, Oct 1992; (2 folders) (Boxes 23, 157)
    - Endorsement Statements, Correspondence For R. Lazio, Oct 1992 (Box 23)
    - Election Recertification Report, Suffolk County, 1992 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Election Recertification Reports, Suffolk County, 1992-1994 (Box 23)
    - Finance Committee Meeting Minutes, (Correspondence, Notes), 26 May 1992; (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Financial Disclosure Statements For Tom Downey, May 1988-Jul 1992; (2 folders) (Boxes 23, 157)
    - Firemen, (Reference, Correspondence), Jun 1992 (Box 23)
    - General Election Recertification Reports, (Election Results), 1992-1998 (Box 23)
    - General Election Results For Senate 1980 – Huntington and Babylon, L.I., 1992 (Boxes 23, 157)
    - General Election Returns, (Recertification Report (Long Island), Nov 1988 (Box 23)
    - General Election Returns For R. Lazio and V.P. 1984 (Long Island), 1992 (Boxes 23, 157)
    - Hispanics, (Reference, Correspondence), Mar-Oct 1992 (Box 23)
    - Interest Group Ratings, (House Vote Descriptions, Downey Voting Record), 1992; (2 folders) (Boxes 23, 157)
    - Irish, (Reference, Correspondence), Sep 1992 (Box 23)
    - Islip Map, No Smoking Sign, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Italians, (Reference, Correspondence), Aug 1992 (Box 23)
    - Labor, (Reference, Correspondence), Jul-Aug 1992 (Box 23)
    - Lazio… For A New Congress, (Press Kit, Announcement Speech, Resume, Press Release), Mar 1992 (Box 23)
    - Legislative Highlights, Accomplishments, (Includes Talking Points For L.I. Forum For Technology), (1 of 2), 1992 (Boxes 23, 157)
    - Letter of Support From National Republican Congressional Committee, (Lazio Bios, Resume, Fact Sheet), 24 Aug 1992 (Box 23)
    - Letters To The Editor, (Misc., From R. Lazio), May-Nov 1992 (Box 23)
    - Long Island Opinion Poll, Feb-Apr 1992 (Boxes 23, 157)
    - National Republican Congressional Com. Survey Findings, National Survey, Feb-Jun 1992 (Box 23)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey Statement of Financial Disbursements, Staff Bios, Quotes, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Opposition Research, (2nd Congressional District Survey Summary), Sep 1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, (Media Overview of Congressional Perks, Airport, Barber Shop, House Gym, Portraits, Etc., Press Clippings), 1991-1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, (Mortgages Held by Tom and Chris Downey), 1992; (2 folders) (Boxes 24, 157)
    - Opposition Research Tips, (Strategy on Campaign Against Tom Downey, Proposed Questions RE: Downey’s Record), Mar-Sep 1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (Downey Speech Notes, Press Clippings, Voting Records), 14 Aug 1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, ("Franking" Abuse), 1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (General Information, Press Clippings and Background Information - Including Newsprint), 1989-1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (House Banking Scandal, Press Clippings, Newsprint), Mar-Oct 1992; (2 folders) (Boxes 24, 157)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (House Banking Scandal, Press Clippings, Including Newsprint), Oct 1991-Aug 1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (House Banking Scandal, Talking Points, Background Material, Mar-Apr 1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (Junket Documentation, ABC News Transcript, (Press clippings), Apr 1991 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (Pay Raises, Press Releases, Correspondence), Oct 1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (‘Pork Barrel’ Spending Documentation, 1992 Congressional Pig Book Summary, Press Clippings), 1991-1992 (Box 24)
    - Opposition Research, Tom Downey, (Post Office Scandal), 1992 (Box 24)
    - "Overview of The Campaign and Its Operations," (analysis of campaign against Tom Downey), 1992 (Box 24)
    - Pharmaceutical Society Political Breakfast, Jul-Aug 1992 (Box 24)
    - Political Almanac Data Sheet, (Candidate Questionnaire For Suffolk Life Newspaper), 1992 (Boxes 24, 157)
    - Polling Places (L.I.) By District, Aug 1992 (Box 24)
    - Position Paper, (Direct Mail Correspondence), Sep-Nov 1992 (Box 24)
    - Post-Mortem Campaign Analysis, (Direct Mail Strategy, Coalition Strategy, Scripts For Television Ads), Aug-Dec 1992 (Box 25)
    - Press Clippings, (Tom Downey Scandals, Includes Newsprint), Mar-Oct 1992 (Box 25)
    - Press Clippings, (Misc. Congressional-Related, Newsprint), Feb-Nov 1992 (Boxes 25, 157)
    - Press Clippings, Printed Material, (Tom Downey, Positive Press, Includes Newsprint), Sep 1984-Oct 1992 (Box 25)
    - Press Clippings, (Tom Downey Scandals), 1990-1992 (Boxes 25, 157)
    - Press Releases, Mar-Nov 1992 (Boxes 25, 157)
    - Press Releases, (Including Misc. Tom Downey Issues), 1992 (Box 25)
    - Press Releases RE: Policy Statements, (Domestic Violence, Health Care, Somalia, Israel, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Press Kit For Lazio Campaign, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Radio Ad Text – Lazio For Congress With Notes, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Radio Advertisement Information, Radio Actuality Info, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Report, Tom Downey Analysis--, Conducted By John Zaher, Campaign Coordinator, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Senior Citizens, Associations, correspondence and contact information, Jul-Aug 1992 (Box 25)
    - Solicitation Letters, Fundraiser Invitations For Rick Lazio Campaign, May-Aug 1992 (Box 25)
    - Survey Summary Report, (Survey Text, Results), Jul-Sep 1992 (Boxes 25, 157)
    - Text (Drafts) For Campaign Materials, (Print and Radio), Jul 1992 (Box 25)
    - Tom Downey Printed Materials, 1981-1992 (Box 25)
    - Tom Downey Printed Materials, 1984-1992 (Boxes 25, 157)
    - Unemployment Benefits, Critique of Downey Plan, (Press Clippings and Background Info, Report on Double Taxation, Lazio Statements, Notes), Aug 1990-Apr 1992; (4 folders) (Boxes 25, 157)
    - Veterans, (Talking Points, Correspondence, Background Material), Jun-Sep 1992 (Box 25)
    - Voting Record – Thomas Downey, (Press Clippings, Background Material), 1981-1992; (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Women’ Associations, Long Island, Jun-Aug 1992 (Box 25)
- Series II. Congressional Papers
  - Appropriations
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Agriculture, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Jan 1997 - Mar 2000 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Education, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Apr 1993-Jun 1996 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Energy, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Apr 1995-Mar 1998 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Environment, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Mar 1993 - Jul 2000; (5 folders) (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Health Care, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Feb 1996 - Apr 2000; (4 folders) (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Health Care/AIDS, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Mar 1993 - Apr 2000 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Health Care/Medicare, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Jan 1998-Oct 1999 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: International Affairs, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Feb 1993 - Sep 2000; (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Israel, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Apr 1993-Nov 1996; (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Senior Citizens, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Nov 1995-Aug 2000 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Transportation, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Apr 1993-Jul 1999; (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Veterans, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), May 1993-Nov 1999 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Welfare, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Jul 1994-Jul 1998 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, Congressional RE: Defense Programs, (Letters Signed by R. Lazio), Apr 1996-Sep 1998 (Box 28)
    - Agriculture, Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed by R. Lazio, Apr 1991-Sep 1999 (Box 28)
    - Amendments- U.N. Funding, Commerce/Justice/State Appropriations, V.A./H.U.D., Treasury-Postal, (Correspondence, House Votes, Background Material), Jun-Aug 1998 (Box 28)
    - Babylon Train Station, (Correspondence), Jul-Aug 1998 (Box 28)
    - Bayshore Schools, Literacy Education and Assessment Partnership, (Correspondence), Mar-Oct 1998 (Box 28)
    - Budget Off Sets, Congressional Questionnaire, Sep 1998 (Box 28)
    - Building Efficiency Through Surface Transportation and Equity Act, (Map and Budget Details), undated (Box 28)
    - Building Efficiency Through Surface Transportation and Equity Act, "East Side Access Project", Press Release, Correspondence), Mar-May 1998; (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, Congressional, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Sent By Rick Lazio), Mar-Oct 1998; (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Defense Program Appropriation Letters, (EDO Corporation/Swims Correspondence), Jul 1998 (Box 28)
    - Dowling College, Global Learning Center, (Press Release, Correspondence), Apr-Oct 1998 (Box 28)
    - Energy and Water Appropriations, (Correspondence), Jan-Jun 1998 (Box 28)
    - Environmental Issues, (Misc. Correspondence, Notes), Jan 1998 - Oct 2000 (Box 28)
    - H.R. 4569 Foreign Appropriations Act, (Legislative Digest, Correspondence), Sep 1998 (Box 28)
    - Long Island Aquarium at Bay Shore, (Funding In Commerce, Justice, State and Judiciary Bill, Senate Report), Sep 1998; (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - New York Cancer Project, Pilot Study, Feb-Dec 1998 (Box 29)
    - Nurse Practitioners, (Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, Background Material, Bill Language), Sep-Oct 1998 (Box 29)
    - Omnibus Appropriations Bill, (Attachments To Bill), Oct 1998 (Box 29)
    - Touro Law Center, (Press Release, Correspondence), Feb-Mar 1998 (Box 29)
    - TWA Flight 800, Reimbursement To Crash Victims, (Correspondence), Sep-Oct 1998 (Box 29)
    - U.S. Army School of Americas, (Correspondence RE: Appropriation Requests), Sep 1998 (Box 29)
    - Appropriations, Misc. (Correspondence, Process-Related Memoranda), Sep 1998-Feb 1999 (Box 29)
    - Memos To R. Lazio, (From Staff, For Approval), Oct 1998-Jul 2000; (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (RE: Educational Programs), Mar 1998 - Aug 2000; (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (RE: Museums/Performing Arts/Educational Centers), Sep 1998 - Jul 2000 (Box 29)
    - Requests, Long Island Aquarium/Bay Shore, (Correspondence, Press Clippings, Background Material, Press Clippings), Aug 1998 - Aug 2000; (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (RE: Community Development - Long Island), Jan 1999 - Mar 2000; (3 folders) (Box 30)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (RE: Education), Nov 1999 (Box 30)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (RE: Health and Human Services Issues), Mar 1999 - Sep 2000 (Box 30)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (RE: Health Care/Human Services), Mar 1999 - Jun 2000 (Box 30)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (RE: Technology/Environment Issues), Feb-Apr 1999 (Box 30)
    - American Association on Health and Disability, Feb-Mar 1999 (Box 30)
    - American Museum For The Preservation of Historic Aircrafts, (Correspondence, Background Material), Feb-May 1999 (Box 30)
    - Appropriation Requests For 1999 (list of appropriations) (Box 30)
    - Appropriation Request Letters From R. Lazio, (Misc. Requests For Funding), 1999-2000 (Box 30)
    - Babylon Citizens Council For The Arts, (Correspondence), Feb-Mar 1999 (Box 30)
    - Requests, Cancer-Related, (Press Releases, Correspondence, Background Material), Oct 2000 (Box 30)
    - Requests, Correspondence From Chairman, Subcommittee On Labor, Health, Human Services, (To R. Lazio), Mar-Apr 1999 (Box 32)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio RE: NYU Medical School, (Correspondence and Background Material), Mar 1999 - Mar 2000 (Box 32)
    - Requests, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, (L.I. Museum of Science and Technology, Includes Background Material), Jan 1999-Mar 1999 (Box 32)
    - Requests, (Staff Correspondence), Dec 1998 - Jan 2000 (Box 32)
    - Cancer Institute of Long Island, (Correspondence, Cancer Institute Reports), Apr 1999 (Box 30)
    - Carnegie Hall’s ‘Third Stage’ Project, (Correspondence), Jun 1999 (Box 30)
    - Cavalese, Italy – Families of Victims U.S. Marine Jet Accident, (Congressional Correspondence), Oct 1998-May 1999 (Box 30)
    - Crime Control/Prevention "Need and Seed" Program (Fact Sheet, Correspondence), 1999 (Box 31)
    - Dowling College Global Learning Center, (Correspondence, Notes, Background Material), Feb-Sep 1999 (Box 31)
    - Economic Opportunity Council of Suffolk, (Correspondence), Mar-May 1999 (Box 31)
    - Head Start Partnerships To Promote Substance Free Communities, (Correspondence), Mar-Apr 1999 (Box 31)
    - Health and Human Services/Long Island, (Appropriation Request List, Correspondence, Background Material), Oct-Nov 1999 (Box 31)
    - Islip Arts Council, (Correspondence), Feb-Mar 1999 (Box 31)
    - Long Island Aquarium At Bay Shore, (Correspondence, Press Clippings, Project Summary), Feb-Mar 1999 (Box 31)
    - Master Crane – Defense Appropriations Bill, (Correspondence), Jan 1999 (Box 31)
    - New York Institute of Technology, (Correspondence, Background Material), 1999 (Box 31)
    - Projects, Appropriations For F.Y. 1999-2001, (Memoranda, Correspondence, Appropriations Process Outline) (Box 31)
    - South Side Hospital, Bay Shore, NY, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jan-Jul 1999 (Box 31)
    - VA H.U.D., (Correspondence), Mar-Jul 1999 (Box 31)
    - Correspondence, Congressional (Letters Signed by R. Lazio), Mar 1999 - Jul 2000; (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Defense Appropriations, (Congressional Correspondence, Background Material), Mar 1999 - Oct 2000 (Box 31)
    - Epidermolysis Bullosa Research, (Correspondence, Reports, Background Materials), Apr 1999 - Apr 2000 (Box 31)
    - Good Samaritan Hospital Medical Center, (Correspondence, Background Material), Feb-Mar 2000 (Box 31)
    - H.R. 1915 "Jennifer’s Law" (Bill Language (Drafts), Letters of Support, Correspondence, Notes, Press Clippings, Lazio Statements), Feb 1999 – Feb 2000; (4 folders) (Box 32)
    - H.R. 5267, Central Islip Court House, (Correspondence, Bill Language), Sep-Oct 2000 (Box 32)
    - Labor, Health and Human Services, (Staff Correspondence), Oct 1999 - Jul 2000 (Box 32)
    - NEA/NEH, (Correspondence, Thank You Letters, Letters of Support and Requests For Funding), Mar 1994 - Oct 2000 (Box 32)
    - N.Y.U. Down Town Hospital Emergency Room, (Correspondence, Project Report), Mar-May 2000 (Box 32)
    - Neurofibromatosis Research, (Correspondence, Draft Letter), Mar 2000 (Box 32)
    - Reductions To Long Island Projects, (Correspondence and Background Material), Oct 1998 - Jan 2000 (Box 32)
    - United Cerebral Policy, (Funding Proposals), Feb-Mar 2000 (Box 32)
  - Campaign Files
    - Campaign Vendors, Consultants, (Reference File), Mar-Jul 1993 (Box 33)
    - Fundraising Event Invitations, Aug-Oct 1993 (Box 33)
    - Political Action Committee, (Fundraiser Event Details, Invite Lists), Mar-Jul 1993 (Box 33)
    - Political Consulting Company Proposals, (Drafts For Campaign Strategies), 1993-1994 (Box 33)
    - Press Releases (pre-campaign), Mar-Dec 1993 (Boxes 33, 157)
    - Accomplishments, Positions Held, Legislation Supported By Rick Lazio, Jun 1994 (Box 33)
    - Arguments For Use Against Assertations Made By James Manfre, Jun-Oct 1994; (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Attorney General, Joe Holland, (Press Kit, Correspondence), Apr 1994 (Box 33)
    - Barristers’ Breakfast, (Flyer, Guest List, Contribution Reports), 13 Oct 1994 (Box 33)
    - Board of Elections District Maps, Suffolk County, 1994-1995 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Bob Dole Presidential Press Material, (News Release, Mailing List), Mar 1995 (Box 33)
    - Brochure Design For Direct Mail Campaign, Oct 1994 (Box 33)
    - Campaign Plan/Rick Lazio For Congress, (Carlyle Gregory Company), 4 Aug 1994 (Box 33)
    - Contribution Letter Template/Draft From Rick Lazio, Sep 1994 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence From Constituents Critical of the Lazio Campaign, Jul-Oct 1994 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence, (Letters of Support), 1994-1996 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence RE: Endorsements, (Press Clippings), Mar-Oct 1994 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence, (thank you), Nov-Dec 1994; (4 folders) (Boxes 33, 34)
    - D’Amato Victory Committee, (1993 Donation Receipts), 1994; (3 folders) (Box 34)
    - Debate Transcript (WLIW), Lazio Vs. Manfre, (Includes Talking Points From Various Speeches, "Media Pointers"), Oct 1994 (Box 34)
    - Economic Initiatives, (Policy Paper, Lazio Economic Policy Speech 1992, Schedule For Congressman Rick Lazio), Oct-Nov 1994 (Box 34)
    - Election District Target List, (Suffolk County Maps), 1994 (Boxes 34, 157)
    - Election Law – State of NY Board of Elections, (Information For Candidates Running For Public Office), Jan 1994 (Box 34)
    - Election Results/Notes, "Elements of a Successful…"(Brochure), Rebuttal/Letter to Jeffrey S. Morosoff, Misc. Correspondence, 1994 (Box 34)
    - Endorsement Letters From Special Interest Groups, Mar-Oct 1994 (Box 34)
    - Fundraising Letter Templates, Mar 1994 (Box 34)
    - General Election Results, (Board of Elections, Suffolk County), Nov 1994 (Box 34)
    - Gun Control – Suffolk Alliance of Sportsmen, (Correspondence, Handgun Control Questionnaire), Apr-Aug 1994 (Box 34)
    - Issue Briefs, Talking Points, (Press Memorandum – Guidance For Dealing With Press), May-Jun 1994 (Box 34)
    - ‘Lazio For Congress ’94 After Action Report’, (Includes Notes of Rick Lazio), 1994 (Box 34)
    - Lease For Lazio Headquarters, Bay Shore L.I., (Memo, "Starting To Look Like a Campaign Office…), 5 Aug 1994 (Boxes 34, 157)
    - Luncheon Honoring Jack Kemp, (Event Notes, Correspondence, Contribution Report, Luncheon Invitation), 20 Jun 1994; (2 folders) (Boxes 35, 157)
    - Luncheon Honoring Sec. of Defense, Dick Cheney, (Correspondence (Copy of Letter From Lazio to Cheney, N.D.) Luncheon Sponsor Card-see legal size for additional materials), 11 Aug 1994; (4 folders) (Boxes 35, 157)
    - Mailing Lists – Clubs and Committees, 1994; (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Manfre, James, (Press Release Draft, Press Clippings), May-Sep 1994 (Box 35)
    - Opinion Poll, (Fabrizio McLaughlin and Associates), Sep 1994; (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Opposition Research, (Negative Ads, Press Against R. Lazio, Press Clips), Jun-Oct 1994 (Box 35)
    - Opposition Research, (Selected Press Clippings, Includes "Republican Contract With America" TV Guide Advertisement Text, 10/14/1994), Sep-Nov 1994 (Box 36)
    - "An Overview of the 1994 Lazio Campaign With Recommendations For Future Campaigns," (Box 36)
    - Physicians Committee For Rick Lazio, (Drafts of Letter From Committee), 1994 (Box 36)
    - Planning and Reference Data For 1994 2nd Congressional District Re-Election Campaign (report), (Includes Campaign Analysis, "Worst Case Scenarios", "Potential Thorny Issues"), 4 Jun 1994 (Box 36)
    - 1994 Post Mortem Notes, (Includes List of "Photography Recommendations" for Candidate) (Box 36)
    - Press Clippings Regarding Lazio/Manfre Race, (WLIW Debate Transcript), 12 Oct 1994 (Box 36)
    - Press Releases, Jan-Apr 1994 (Boxes 36, 157)
    - Press and Correspondence RE: Opponent James Manfre, Lazio Volunteer List, 1994 (Box 36)
    - Press Releases (Includes Draft Letter To Editor, see legal size for additional press releases), May-Oct 1994; (2 folders) (Boxes 36, 157)
    - Public Opinion Survey, (Survey Drafts, Questionnaire), Sep 1994 (Box 36)
    - Report – Comparison of Congressional Agendas – Republican vs. Democrat, May 1994 (Box 36)
    - Republican National Committee, (Talking Points, Issue Summaries), Jun-Nov 1994 (Box 36)
    - Scheduled Events For R. Lazio Calendar, Feb-Oct 1994 (Box 36)
    - Television Production/Advertisements, (Shot Lists, Scripts, Air Time Lists, Memos To R. Lazio RE: Media Updates), Sep-Oct 1994 (Box 36)
    - Walker International Transportation Reception, (Event Memo, Invitation), Jun 1994 (Box 36)
    - Contribution Cards and Lists, 1994 – CONFIDENTIAL (Box 162)
    - Contribution Call List, 1994 – CONFIDENTIAL (Box 162)
    - White House Swearing In Event Logistics, Dec 1994-Jan 1995 (Box 36)
    - Fundraiser Invitation, (Kessler and Associates), Oct-Nov 1995 (Box 36)
    - Fundraising Consultant Proposal, Apr 1995 (Box 36)
    - Holiday Luncheon, (Correspondence, Schedule of Event, Sponsorship Card, Notes), Nov 1996 (Box 36)
    - Opinion Poll, (Produced By Marketing, Inc.), Jul 1995 (Box 36)
    - Overview and Critique Coalitions and Political Fieldwork, (Lazio For Congress 1994 (campaign report), 1995 (Box 36)
    - Analysis, New York District 2, Political Science Term Paper, 21 Mar 1996 (Box 36)
    - Award, (60 Plus Association, Press Release), Sep 1996 (Boxes 36, 157)
    - Budget For Campaign, Campaign Overview, Goals Defined For 1996 Campaign, Fundraising Plan (Box 36)
    - Campaign Budgets, Financial Summaries, 1996 (Boxes 36, 157)
    - Campaign Closing Analysis Report, (Staffing, Consultant and Communication Info, Outreach Strategy, Fundraising, Volunteer Info), 15 Dec 1996 (Box 36)
    - Draft Texts, Photo Layouts For Printed Materials, 1996 (Box 36)
    - Election Targeting, (Notes, Suffolk County Voter Registration Tally Sheets), Jan-Jul 1996 (Box 36)
    - Election Targeting, (Suffolk County Voter Registration Tally Sheets, Election District Swap Analysis), 1996 (Boxes 37, 157)
    - Endorsements, (Press Releases, Correspondence), Feb-Nov 1996 (Box 37)
    - Fundraising/Event Logistics, (Correspondence, Budgets, Notes, Memoranda), Jul-Sep 1996 (Box 37)
    - General Election, (Suffolk County Map With 1996 Election Results) (Boxes 37, 157)
    - Islip Committee Thank You Correspondence Supporting Bob Dole’s Presidential Race, (Mailing Lists) CONFIDENTIAL, Jan 1995 – Feb 1996 (Box 37)
    - Opinion Poll, (Survey Of Voters, NY 2nd District, (Fabrizio McLaughlin and Associates), 17 Sep 1996 (Box 37)
    - Opposition Research, (Notes, Press Clippings), Mar-Oct 1996; (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Opposition Research, (Press Clippings, newsprint), 1996 (Boxes 38, 157)
    - Political Coalitions, (Correspondence, Contact Information, Includes 12/2/96 Letter From Lazio-Hispanic Advisory Board), 1996 (Box 38)
    - Print Media, Direct Mail, Graphic Design Layouts, 1996 (Box 38)
    - Public Opinion Survey Drafts, Sep 1996 (Box 38)
    - Reference File – AFL-CIO/Presidential Impeachment, (Correspondence), Feb-Sep 1996 (Box 38)
    - Reference File – Economy, (Correspondence, Press Clippings), Jan-Oct 1996 (Box 38)
    - Reference File – Veterans, (Correspondence, Talking Points), Apr-Jul 1996 (Box 38)